--------------------------------------------------------
BIOGRAPHY
--------------------------------------------------------

Mr. 94 was one of the least useful of Crocodile's minions in the Baroque Works organization. His strange power only allowed him to slowly become a bastardization of the people around him, turning him into some sort of uncontrollable hybrid of all the pirates in the Great Blue. With his partner, Ms. Boxing Day, and their pet, Gun Krieg, a refrigerator that ate a Human Human fruit, they were a force that some assumed would be difficult to reckon with, but they were never seen from because no one told them the location of Baroque Works'  hideouts. After it's fall, Mr. 94 and his crew fled from Baroque Works to distant lands in search of other insane dictators for whom he could ride their coattails to victory, but no one would require the services of such a miserable agent.

...I just really like One Piece.

--------------------------------------------------------
MOVELIST
--------------------------------------------------------

----------------
BASICS
----------------

LP + LK - ""

MP + MK - ""

HP + HP - "Kachi Kachi"
	- A powerup move similar to X-Factor that can be used for 1 power bar. It can be used in the middle of any attack, provided that you are on the ground, or while blocking. Resets damage in combos and gives the player a power boost.

Back + HK while in midair - ""
	- A basic kick that knocks the opponent into the wall instead of downward

F, F, P or P while running - ""
	- A running kick that knocks the opponent into the air.

F, F, K or K while running - ""
	- A jumping knee attack that knocks the opponent upward. Press any kick button to follow it up with a wallbouncing attack.

----------------
SPECIALS
----------------
(EX specials can be preformed by pressing either two punches or two kicks)

QCF, P  - "Moku Moku"
	- Sprays projectiles in a direction depenadant on the strength of the punch button.
	
QCB, P - "Mato Mato"
	- Counter move. LP counters crouching attacks, MP counters standing and aireal attacks, and HP counters projectile attacks.
	
QCF, K - "Ushi Ushi"
	- Preforms a dashing elbow forward, its length depending on the strength of the punch button. You can follow this up with 2 more punches to continue with a combo. The LP variation hits low. The MP variation is an overhead.
	
QCB, K - "Hikyu Hikyu"
	- Lunges forward and kicks the opponent skyward.

----------------
LEVEL 1 SUPERS
----------------

QCF, QCF, LP - "Hiso Hiso"
	- A swarm of rabid bee projectiles.
	
QCF, QCF, LK - "Sube Sube"
	- Dr. Kiln's patented hyper combo. First attack hits low.
	
QCF, QCF, MK - "Suke Suke"
	- More combo crap. Immune to projectiles while invisible.
	
QCB, QCB, LK - "Shari Shari"
	- A rolling tackle. Last hit knocks the opponent backwards.
	
QCB, QCB, MK - Bara Bara
	- Creates a tornado of stuff around Mr. 94.

----------------
LEVEL 2 SUPERS
----------------

QCF, QCF, HP - "Pika Pika"
	- IT'S A BEEEAM~

--------------------------------------------------------
THANK YA KINDLY
--------------------------------------------------------

Mouser
	- For allowing (I.E. having no idea about) me to fuck up your character like a week after you released it, which fyi was just REALLY ironic timing as I had been planning to edit K' for a while.
	
MelvanaInChains
	- If I didn't have a reason to put you here, I'd do it anyway.

Yoshi348
	- Lovable beta testin' dinosaur